<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Shubham Kukreti</title><link>https://www.shubhamkukreti.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Shubham Kukreti</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:25:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.shubhamkukreti.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On a New Voyage</title><link>https://www.shubhamkukreti.com/on-a-new-voyage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:25:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://www.shubhamkukreti.com/on-a-new-voyage/</guid><description>It’s always about journey, on a new voyage now I’m writing this as I’ve just boarded Caltrain from San Francisco to Palo Alto. The Wi-Fi won’t connect, but the views are incredible. Emotions? All over the place. So, like always, I’m thinking about the road that got me here.
At Nine Summer break at my mamu’s place. He had a Windows 95 PC, basically wonder to a kid who’d only seen computers in rich people’s houses.</description></item><item><title>Creator Sum Value &amp; Creator Factor</title><link>https://www.shubhamkukreti.com/creator-sum-value-creator-factor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 19:59:44 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://www.shubhamkukreti.com/creator-sum-value-creator-factor/</guid><description>Readers might feel lost or not making sense of it. Totally alright. I am still working on it.
While using the word platform. I have two different context in mind. One is that shows a fixed metrics (UI) biased. Other is the protocol level or the underlying system.
Creator Value (CV) Creator Value is a mathematical fan-weighted value of a creator. $$ CV = C_i \times F_i $$
Creator Sum Value (CSV) Creator Sum Value is the sum of all the Creator Values of a creator on all the platforms.</description></item><item><title>Why I am here</title><link>https://www.shubhamkukreti.com/why-i-am-here/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 22:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://www.shubhamkukreti.com/why-i-am-here/</guid><description>tl;dr - I don&amp;rsquo;t know I am an overthinker. I love to dive into more profound thoughts. Sometimes my thoughts are around real-world situations or experiences; sometimes, I develop different constructs and think from all different sides.
This over-thinking behaviour has led me to develop a habit of researching or going down the rabbit hole and not bringing conclusions from just a single side. And I love it.
Currently, I am learning about decentralised systems, zero-knowledge proofs, deep space and sometimes about ancient Hindu scriptures.</description></item></channel></rss>